https://dermoscopy-ids.org/about-international-dermoscopy-society/privacy-policy/

Forum Login
Forum Archive (Old Forum)
Forum Login
Forum Archive (Old Forum)
Privacy Policy
The International Dermoscopy Society (IDS) is serious about protecting your privacy. Any information we collect is solely for the purpose of enhancing your membership experience.
This site may request personally identifiable data from you (“Personal Information”), which may include your e-mail address, domain name (where possible) or other personal information such as your address, telephone number, etc. In addition, our web server automatically recognizes and stores your e-mail address or your domain name (where possible) when you log onto our site, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, and aggregate information about what pages on our site you visit or access.
The Personal Information described above will be collected solely by IDS. We use email to communicate with you about IDS activities and news. Personal Information is used by IDS to assist in serving you more effectively. Personal Information is also used by IDS to improve the content of our web page, to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual member, to notify members about updates to our web site, and/or to contact members for issues related to IDS.
In addition, at any time you may request to correct the Personal Information, request that such information should be removed from IDS database, or request that IDS no longer solicit you either by e-mail, telephone, regular mail or by any other means. To make any request described above, send an email to the president of the society. When contacting us, please be sure to provide us with your exact e-mail address, name, address and/or telephone number(s) in order to be sure we handle your request correctly.
By using this site, you are agreeing to the terms set forth in IDS Privacy Policy. IDS reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.
Search
About IDS
Articles and Aims
Copyright Information
Privacy Policy
General Terms
Search
Best Forum Cases
Hot TopicsForum (registration)
Dermoscopy on PubmedDifferential diagnosis of Lisch nodules under dermoscopy.Join our forum!
Join our Facebook page
And our Facebook discussion group!
Join our forum!
This site is made possible in part by unrestricted educational grants from:
Website by Qbrains Complete Digital Marketing Agency and Beeasy.eu
Type and Press “enter” to Search
